# Elaina Yutong Zhong

702/85 O'Connor st Chippendale NSW 2008 10411350871 yutong990624@gmail.com https://yutong990624.wixsite.com/ yutong @yutongzhong\_

Graduating from the University of Technology, Sydney (UTS) in 2021 with a Bachelor of Design in Fashion & Textiles with electives specializing in Machine Knitting, Fashion Photography, Screen Printing and Textile Dyeing.

Learning Ability: Strong willingness and ability to learn and adapt quickly, easily able to integrate into a team. Able to work flexibly depending on the needs of the company or project.

Personal Ability: Passionate and dedicated interest in working in the fashion industry, cheerful and optimistic personality and good at communication. Able to work efficiently at a variety of tasks and under pressure. Great at working individually and within a team.

### Education

Bachelor of Design in Fashion & Textiles University of Technology, Sydney (UTS) Expected to graduate in 2021

Degree in Marketing

Kaplan Higher Education Academy, Singapore

2015 - 2017

## Relevant Experience

Studio Assistant (Casual)

Lorna Murray Apparel (Sydney)

Aug 2020- Present

- Quality control, assurance and stock management including inventory management within Shopify.
- Picking and packaging online retail orders for e-commerce store.
- · Product photography and styling
- Assisting with wholesale order fulfillment, logistics, customer relations and other admin tasks
- · General studio assistance and maintenance

#### Intern

By Johnny (Sydney) May 2021

- Photography; assisting with photoshoots and fittings for new season styles, shooting behind the scenes content.
- Product display and merchandising; displaying and organising showroom, documenting and taking pictures.
- Production assistant, working on sample fabric management and organisation, assisting designers with organising fabrics and swatches.

## Relevant Experience

# Textiles Designer Assistant Affirm Heart Limited (Guangdong, China) Oct 2018 - Feb 2019

- Sourcing fabrics and major textile exhibitions and fabric markets, research and knowledge of fabric trends in fashion.
   Understanding and knowledge of fabric types and organising fabric swatches and trims.
- Assisting with textiles production and sampling for internationally renowned fashion companies such as Sass & Bide and Camilla and Marc. Working on product development for new textile fabrications for sample production.
- Communicating with artisans about lace, embroidery and beading design work.,
- Liaising with textile suppliers regarding fabric quality and price.
- · Drawing technical sketches for samples and new styles

#### Retail Fashion Sales Associate

Little Red Riding Hood Children's Clothing Store (Guangdong, China)

### Feb 2018 - Sep 2018

- · Managing retail point of sales and transactions
- High-quality customer service experience, assisting customers with styling and product selection
- Merchandising and product display within the store

### **Skills**

- Language Ability: Fluent in Mandarin and Cantonese
- Software Skills: Proficient in Adobe Suite including Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign, Coreldraw and Microsoft Office.
   Currently learning CLO virtual fashion software.
- Photography Skills: Capable at using digital camera technology, including image editing.